citybunch.in 2009-12-01

# Privacy Policy CityBunch INDIA Yellow Pages

## CityBunch Privacy Policy

This policy covers CityBunch's treatment of the personally identifiable information that CityBunch collects when customers or visitors use our web site or our services. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CityBunch does not own or control, or to people who CityBunch does not employ or manage.

CityBunch is the sole owner of the information collected on the site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to anyone except for the purpose of promoting your business. In addition, CityBunch will send this information to companies or people when:

\- we have your consent to share the information;  
\- we need to share the information to provide the product or service you have requested;  
\- we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes; or   
\- we find that your actions on our web site violate CityBunch's Terms of Service. 

It could happen that CityBunch would share statistical information with our partners and advertisers. However, this is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

When you register with CityBunch, we ask you to divulge certain personally identifiable information. Once this has been done, you are no longer anonymous to us. CityBunch also collects this information when you use certain CityBunch products or services, and when you enter promotions or competitions.

CityBunch has installed and uses products which collect statistical data from our visitors. This data collection does not violate any laws, confidentiality, or other obligations between CityBunch and our visitors. We do not collect any personally identifiable information from visitors of our website. Our software partners who supply our statistical tools do not sell, share, or distribute any private or personal information with any third parties.

Some of our business partners, such as advertisers, may use cookies on our site. However, we have no control or access over these cookies. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies rule, not ours. Other companies do not have access to CityBunch cookies.

CityBunch may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web site.

If you feel that CityBunch is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact the Webmaster.

We use an outside shipping company to provide specific services. When a user signs up for these services, we will share the necessary information for the shipping company to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use this information except for the purpose of providing these services.
